https://www.missinganimalresponse.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Missing Animal Response Network
Skip to main content Skip to footerMissing Animal Response NetworkLost Pet Recovery Training By Kat AlbrechtHome
Pet Detective Directory
Don’t Call Your Dog!
Tag Your Car
How Long Can Scent Survive?
Lost Pet Behaviors
My Life!
Privacy Policy
The Missing Animal Response Network Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our services.
Email Information
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to this website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in each such email.
Notice of New Services and Changes
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to this website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in each such email.
Certain Disclosures
We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.
What About Other Websites Linked to This Site?
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our site to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including sites which have a link on our site, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.
Your Consent
By using this site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
Footer
Testimonials
GREAT ADVICE AND SUPPORTHello from St. Louis, Missouri. I wanted to say I can’t thank Lisa enough for helping me through my lost pet last week. Pebbles was missing for 6 days and we did everything Lisa said. Her great ideas she helped calm my nerves and last night the day before Lisa was heading to St. Louis… Read more “GREAT ADVICE AND SUPPORT”Brian FleetwoodTrailing Peanut the hairless pupOn February 14 after just moving in to our new home 4 days earlier our little 17lb American hairless terrier, Peanut somehow came out of her collar and ran off. We did as most would do and immediately started to look for her and put flyers up. The following day as our panic was growing… Read more “Trailing Peanut the hairless pup”KellyDON’T MESS WITH THE REST WHEN YOU CAN HAVE THE BESTI’ve known Bravo personally for several years including during all of his training & I have seen the incredible progress he has made. Bravo was born to do this job & he loves it. There is no other dog I would ever trust the way I trust Bravo & his amazing loving owner/trainer, Balynda Brown… Read more “DON’T MESS WITH THE REST WHEN YOU CAN HAVE THE BEST”LeeP.E.I. loves Mike Chapman!!Recently, we reached out to Mike Chapman for his expertise in helping to find a very shy dog on the run. In my 40 years of owning dogs, this is the first time I’ve ever had to deal with something like this. Mike accepted our case, and led the way with knowledge, compassion, optimism, and… Read more “P.E.I. loves Mike Chapman!!”LeahTrailing Peanut the Hairless PupOn February 14 after just moving in to our new home 4 days earlier our little 17 lb American hairless terrier, Peanut somehow came out of her collar and ran off. We did as most would do and immediately started to look for her and put flyers up. The following day as our panic was… Read more “Trailing Peanut the Hairless Pup”Went Above and Beyond for Our New Rescue This Holiday Season.Tracey and Jeff (Luzerne County Pet Recovery Services) went above and beyond for our new rescue this holiday season. Samwell has only lived in our home for four days when this foster family penned “escape artist” ran through a closing door on December 19th, 2019. From the moment we reached out for help, Tracey was… Read more “Went Above and Beyond for Our New Rescue This Holiday Season.”Jen and Jeff Partyka, Glenburn PAP.E.I. Loves Mike ChapmanRecently, we reached out to Mike Chapman for his expertise in helping to find a very shy dog on the run. In my 40 years of owning dogs, this is the first time I’ve ever had to deal with something like this. Mike accepted our case, and led the way with knowledge, compassion, optimism, and… Read more “P.E.I. Loves Mike Chapman”Belinda Brown brought my dog home to meI am so thankful that MAR exists Belinda Brown is a hero to me. She swung into action with useful advice and coaching. It was her advice to set up food stations that saved my dog, Xin. Thank you is not enough to express my gratitude. Xin is very much a part of me that… Read more “Belinda Brown brought my dog home to me”INVALUABLE INFORMATIONHi Kat, I wanted to tell you how invaluable the information on lost/displaced indoor cats is on your website. The information was spot on about the cats behavior when lost outside their home. Our visiting family left our front door open long enough for our Gordy to escape. This happened late at night after we… Read more “INVALUABLE INFORMATION”Anne R.Balynda’s DedicationBalynda, who has now become a friend, is excellent at what she does. Both she and Bravo are wonderful. They will be IMMENSELY valuable to North Carolina when they graduate. We are lucky!!Jenny L.Wonderful Caring PeopleTeddy, Lynn, and Winston worked tirelessly for 12+ hours each day for 13 days! Niko was lost at the beach on Long Island, NY.. VERY difficult area.. Niko traveled 5-6 miles in different directions… He was spotted by several people… who tried to “catch” him… there were a lot of snags along… Read more “Wonderful Caring People”I Owe You GuysDeborah Cooke and Katie Albright both helped me greatly in getting my Archie back home! I’m so, so very grateful. Just by speaking on the phone and following their advice resulted in my getting my cat back after 13 days of him being gone. Deborah’s suggestion to drip Mackerel juice in a star leading to… Read more “I Owe You Guys”Bonnie and Bodhi Search TeamI cant even begin to explain how amazing Bonnie Hale and her search dog Bodhi are!! Our cat Westie, new to outdoors and the area, went missing 12 days ago. Even with daily searches and 400 lost cat posters, several hopeful but deadend sightings we couldnt find her. Researching and reaching out to… Read more “Bonnie and Bodhi Search Team”Lost Cat FOUND with Consultation!“Annalisa Berns is a true detective who works methodically but also empathizes with pet owners and can think like a lost cat! She got in touch with us immediately, created a map (specific to our neighborhood) to guide our search, developed likely scenarios preventing our kitty from returning home and gave us a plan of… Read more “Lost Cat FOUND with Consultation!”Tiffany & RoeyGus Found Thanks to Annalisa Berns and Search Dogs June and Hope“It was eleven days of pain. Gus went missing the afternoon of February 12th. After searching, posting posters, flyers and driving all over, we called Annalisa. She came over on February 22nd, with Search Dogs June and Hope. As she tracked Gus’s scent trail, she kept us posted with GPS maps that reflected his exact… Read more “Gus Found Thanks to Annalisa Berns and Search Dogs June and Hope”2nd ChanceWhen I first contacted Tracey, my cat, Chance had been missing for 4 weeks. We had just moved into a new townhouse and at 5:30am I let him outside to go to the bathroom. I accidentally fell asleep while giving him “a minute.” When I woke up around 6:10 I panicked and searched the bushes… Read more “2nd Chance”Thank YouI met Tracey through a mutual friend on July 12th. I coordinate a transport for Mary Ann Morris Animal Society out of Bamberg SC and we had a dog get loose on transport on April 21st – Luci. We were all devastated and desperately tried for the next 4 and a half months to get… Read more “Thank You”Thank you!I met Tracey through a mutual friend on July 12th. I coordinate a transport for Mary Ann Morris Animal Society out of Bamberg SC and we had a dog get loose on transport on April 21st – Luci. We were all devastated and desperately tried for the next 4 and a half months to get… Read more “Thank you!”Suzanne Scott LOST PET HELP LEADS TO THE RECOVERY OF DUKEJust wanted to say thank you for posting the information about lost cat behaviour on the web. It was instrumental in finding my cat Duke who suddenly vanished into thin air (or so it seemed) last Tuesday. I did the usual – stuffing lost cat flyers into 200 plus mailboxes in my area, talking to… Read more “LOST PET HELP LEADS TO THE RECOVERY OF DUKE”The Adventures of Pi and LokiI rescued these brothers in October of 2016. Both these cats are Curious/ Clowns, however Pi is a little more shy and reserved. They both settled in to farm life beautifully. I did often worry about them because they like to get into vehicles if a door or window is open…….. then on October 23… Read more “The Adventures of Pi and Loki”2 Lost CatsA week my 2 indoor only cats got out through a broken window screen. You advised in an article that I should thoroughly search close by neighbors properties and I found them within an hour hiding in a delapetated shed at the back of my neighbor’s property just two houses away. They were completely quiet… Read more “2 Lost Cats”By Grace AloneTracey is a naturally gifted pet detective, mentor, and friend. Her passion for locating missing animals is evident when you work with her. She is motivated, driven, and focused on the MAR techniques essential to successfully and humanely recovering beloved missing pets. Recently, we worked together to capture a male mixed breed hound named Fred… Read more “By Grace Alone”Susan to the RescueSusan Long quite simply saved the day. There is so much emotional baggage tied up in that dumb, lovable, exasperating dog (and now he’s even more expensive). From the moment Susan answered the phone, she was all in on our behalf, arriving a few hours later to galvanize us into action. Oliver was found within… Read more “Susan to the Rescue”TRANSPORT ESCAPEOn June 30th, 2018 I was devastated to find out that Tashi, my 1-and-a-half-year-old Lhasa Apso, got loose at the Granville North Carolina rest stop, from a dog transporter who was supposed to drive him from our old home in Northern VA to our new home in Tampa, FL. The County Humane Society, Animal Control,… Read more “TRANSPORT ESCAPE”By Grace AloneDear Kat, I am writing you in response to my interactions with Tracey over the last few weeks. Tracey is a naturally gifted pet detective, mentor, and friend. Her passion for locating missing animals is evident when you work with her. She is motivated, driven, and focused on the MAR techniques essential to successfully and… Read more “By Grace Alone”It Takes A VillageI met Tracey Dreibelbis on day seven trying to catch Fred whom had escaped from my neighbor’s boarding facility. She was very professional and informed me of Fred’s patterns over the past few days. She came up with a plan to catch Fred using my fenced in yard. We baited my yard with McDonald cheese… Read more “It Takes A Village”Jamie McCallumEvery Shelter or Animal Rescue Group Should Take This Training CourseI had already been helping my wife Tracey with MAR work and she had won the MAR course during one of Kat’s training seminars. So I decided to take the course and fill in the gaps of what I had already learned and what I was missing. To my surprise I had opened a door… Read more “Every Shelter or Animal Rescue Group Should Take This Training Course”Jeff Chopick, Kingston PALuzerne County Pet Recovery ServicesYou Helped Me Save My 2 Lost CatsA week my 2 indoor only cats got out through a broken window screen. You advised in an article that I should thoroughly search close by neighbors properties and I found them within an hour hiding in a delapetated shed at the back of my neighbor’s property just two houses away. They were completely quiet… Read more “You Helped Me Save My 2 Lost Cats”JD LoweryInstumental In Finding My CatJust wanted to say thank you for posting the information about lost cat behaviour on the web. It was instrumental in finding my cat Duke who suddenly vanished into thin air (or so it seemed) last Tuesday. I did the usual – stuffing lost cat flyers into 200 plus mailboxes in my area, talking to… Read more “Instumental In Finding My Cat”Alison HeadlandChanged My Life – Traci M DurangoI took Kat’s on line course and it changed my life. Even if you choose to not have a search dog you will learn the science behind how, where and why animals go missing and what you can do to helpTraci M Durango, ColoradoI Couldn’t Wait Until the Next Week’s Lesson Arrived – Susan L.I took the class expecting it to be superficial information that I already knew. I couldn’t have been more wrong! This class is in depth, research based, and very professional. I couldn’t wait until the next week’s lesson arrived. I highly recommend it for anyone that is helping to recover lost pets.Susan L.An Incredibly In-Depth and Informative Course – Sharon MI had the opportunity to take the MAR 10 week course with Kat Albrecht over the winter. I found it to be an incredibly in-depth and informative course. Not only in the volumes of well thought out but professionally presented information she presented but also in the weekly telephone support she provided. Kat is truly… Read more “An Incredibly In-Depth and Informative Course – Sharon M”Sharon M -
Pembroke, NHKat is a Gem as A Teacher, You Will Be Learning From the Best! – Karin N.I had bought Kat Albrecht’s books wanting to have more information in “Search and Rescue” comparing it with “Map Dowsing” the way I search for missing animals. I was happy when I found out about the Mar 10 week certified course “Kat Albrecht” was teaching. I sure was looking forward to my first class and… Read more “Kat is a Gem as A Teacher, You Will Be Learning From the Best! – Karin N.”Karin N.One of the Best Courses I Have Ever Taken – Judene D.After many years in lost pet recovery, I found this course still taught me a great deal. It was one of the best courses I have ever taken. Kat’s knowledge, skill, experience, humor, compassion, and dedication make this a wonderful learning opportunity. I also find the ways Kat provides for MAR graduates to communicate with… Read more “One of the Best Courses I Have Ever Taken – Judene D.”Judene D. -
MAR Volunteer and Maine Lost Dog Recovery Volunteer, MaineLoved the MAR Training – Jim B. Cincinnati, OhioLoved the MAR training and the insights from my MARs classmates. Very beneficial information in how to up my skills in searches for lost pets!Jim B. Cincinnati, OhioDefinitely so worth it! – Jennifer H. ComerThe knowledge I gained and continue to learn from the MAR training is amazing, I have always tried to find pets. Now I believe I am acquiring proper, proven,skills to reunite more families. The connections made, because of the MAR class, with other like-minded people, to share experiences and advice is irreplaceable. Definitely so worth… Read more “Definitely so worth it! – Jennifer H. Comer”Jennifer H. Comer, GeorgiaThe Classes Were Convenient and Informative – Crystal C.I was delighted to take a MAR training course from Kat. I was impressed with the details, depth, and the variety of materials shared with us during our course. The classes were convenient, informative and delivered with skill and an obvious passion for passing on her experience and knowledge to others so that more people… Read more “The Classes Were Convenient and Informative – Crystal C.”Crystal C., Certified Professional Dog Trainer and MAR volunteer, PennsylvaniaTechniques learned through this course are credited for saving many lives and reuniting familiesThe MAR course helped me understand the behavior of a lost pet and the science of a search. The techniques learned through this course are credited for saving many lives and reuniting families.Bonnie B.,Puyallup, WashingtonRoaming Paws Lost Pet ServicesHighly recommend MAR courseI found the MAR course incredibly useful and learnt and enjoyed learning about lost pet behavior as well as the behavior of owners and finders. Would highly recommend the training to anyone working in the field of lost pet recovery.Anna R. Canberra, Australia
Home
About Kat
Books
Pet Detective Directory
Blog
Don’t Call Your Dog!
All rights reserved. • Lost Pet Recovery Training by Kat Albrecht
•
Privacy Policy
